<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog</id>
    <title>Dynamo Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-08-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Dynamo Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://dynamofinance.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault audited]]></title>
        <id>https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/vault-audited</id>
        <link href="https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/vault-audited"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last month has been exciting in terms of the progress we have been able to make a lot of progress.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The last month has been exciting in terms of the progress we have been able to make a lot of progress.
Our ERC-4626 vault was examined by <a href="https://twitter.com/IAm0x52" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">0x52</a> in a four-day smart-contract security audit.
Our smart-contract team (led by Ben and Sajal) were able to fix all highly and medium classified issues - no critical issue was found.</p><p>The <a href="https://dynamofinance.github.io/docs/security" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">full audit report</a> is available in our docs and we are currently preparing our testnet deployments.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Scherry</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/scherrey</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Sajal Kayan</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/sajal</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Eike Caldeweyher</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/f3rmion</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="vault" term="vault"/>
        <category label="erc-4626" term="erc-4626"/>
        <category label="audit" term="audit"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault development finished]]></title>
        <id>https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/vault-finished</id>
        <link href="https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/vault-finished"/>
        <updated>2023-05-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We finished our ERC-4626 vault development and the boosted pool integration in the Balancer ecosystem!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We finished our ERC-4626 vault development and the boosted pool integration in the Balancer ecosystem!
After an internal code review from Balancer we received also the first tranche of our grant and
are now moving forward to the first smart-contract audit.
The first audit will most probably be happening in early June, and we plan to get a second competitive audit on top.</p><p>Keep tuned!</p><p>Cheers,</p><p>ehjc</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Eike Caldeweyher</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/f3rmion</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="vault" term="vault"/>
        <category label="erc-4626" term="erc-4626"/>
        <category label="balancer" term="balancer"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vault development]]></title>
        <id>https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/vault-development</id>
        <link href="https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/vault-development"/>
        <updated>2023-01-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy new year Dynamos!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Happy new year Dynamos! 🎉</p><p>We are progressing in the development of our ERC-4626 vault.
We plan to apply this vault structure within our decentralised base pool that we deploy as a boosted pool on Balancer V2.</p><p>A general diagram for the infrastructure can be seen below, however, an overall overview will be posted as a separat part of the documentation.
Furthermore, we will update this blog post with new insights about development steps.</p><p><img loading="lazy" alt="Vault" src="/assets/images/vault-c1109c70e909563c54d2060132092d99.png" width="1007" height="771" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>Above the blue parts (Assetmanager) are Vyper contracts that have been developed internally within the past months.
Those asset manager interact with linear pools as developed by Balancer.
All linear pools are incorporated in a boosted stable pool.
Hence we are able to shift most of the liquidity to the ERC-4626 vaults, which will then be deployed to different lending markets (e.g., AAVE or Compound).</p><p>The proportions of the underlying lending markets are defined by asset-specific Strategies.
In order to participate as a Strategist, a new set of weights has to be proposed.
This new set of weights has to increase the APY of the asset-specific vault.
If it does, the Strategy goes live and the Strategist earns part of the revenue that is collected while the Strategy is active.</p><p>The governance part of the ERC-4626 vault will be released soon as well.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithHideOnScrollNavbar_WYt5" id="update-2023-01-13">Update 2023-01-13<a href="#update-2023-01-13" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Update 2023-01-13" title="Direct link to Update 2023-01-13">​</a></h3><p>Since the Balancer infrastructure does not allow an easy solution for custom asset manager yet (maybe in Balancer V3?), we decided to interface with the ERC-4626 vaults directly.</p><p><img loading="lazy" alt="Vault-2" src="/assets/images/2023-01-13_vault-2cbf7e314d84e99184fe25c40f79aa86.png" width="1007" height="771" class="img_ev3q"></p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Eike Caldeweyher</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/f3rmion</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Scherry</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/scherrey</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="vault" term="vault"/>
        <category label="erc-4626" term="erc-4626"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Development grant]]></title>
        <id>https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/balancer-grant</id>
        <link href="https://dynamofinance.github.io/blog/balancer-grant"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team at Balancer Grants is proud to announce the approval of the grant application by Dynamo to use Balancer V2 architecture to build a yield aggregator for decentralised stablecoins and other assets such as Ethereum staking derivatives by aggregating lending markets such as Aave and Compound.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The team at Balancer Grants is proud to announce the approval of the grant application by Dynamo to use Balancer V2 architecture to build a yield aggregator for decentralised stablecoins and other assets such as Ethereum staking derivatives by aggregating lending markets such as Aave and Compound.</p><p>By aggregating lending markets, Dynamo generates an optimised yield for depositors that comes from shifting TVL between different lending markets in order to take advantage of shifts in interest rates as they occur in real time and generate an optimised lending yield.</p><p>Dynamo plans to use this infrastructure in order to generate yield optimised liquidity pools for decentralized stablecoins and other assets such as Ethereum staking derivatives by tapping into the Balancer V2 architecture in order to build liquidity solutions on top of the Balancer Boosted Pool framework. Furthermore, by tapping into Balancer’s asset management capabilities Dynamo can develop yield optimised liquidity pools for decentralised stablecoins and other assets on top of its base pools turning them into a highly active liquidity layer.</p><p>Through this grant, Balancer aims for the end result to be a new boosted pool use case of ERC4626 bringing more liquidity and fees to the protocol and set a precedent for more people to build.</p><blockquote><p>“Dynamo is taking Balancer boosted pools to the next level with their yield aggregation vaults that optimizes yield across the major money markets. It’s great that defi teams are starting to realize the potential of Balancer boosted pools to create sustainable yield for liquidity providers.”</p><p>-- <cite>Mike B, Balancer Grants Committee Member &amp; Maxi</cite></p></blockquote><blockquote><p>“After spending a lot of time looking for an AMM solution to build upon, the Balancer V2 architecture stood out to us as the best option because of its unique boosted pool infrastructure. This architecture enables us to offer a capital efficient solution for liquidity providers who are looking for the best way to deploy their capital. We believe that Balancer is poised to grow into a systemically important defi lego because of its extremely vibrant ecosystem and we are very happy to support it.”</p><p>-- <cite>Rohmanus Dynamo team member</cite></p></blockquote><h2 class="anchor anchorWithHideOnScrollNavbar_WYt5" id="about-dynamo">About Dynamo<a href="#about-dynamo" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to About Dynamo" title="Direct link to About Dynamo">​</a></h2><p>Dynamo is a yield generation platform that aims to serve liquidity providers by turning their previously idle liquidity into an active resource through the use of lending markets. Dynamo achieves this through the use of Dynamo vaults which maintain a diversified exposure profile in whitelisted lending venues such as Aave, Compound and Euler aiming to generate an optimised lending yield by shifting liquidity around in order to stay on top of interest rate fluctuations. By taking advantage of defi’s inherent composability Dynamo can become a building block for capital efficient liquidity provision and other defi activities.</p><p>By activating previously idle liquidity, Dynamo offers an enhanced user experience to liquidity providers through the use of Balancer’s boosted pool architecture. Dynamo is building on top of the boosted pool architecture in order to offer a suite of yield optimised liquidity pools by starting with a liquidity solution for the decentralised stablecoin community through the Dynamo base pool. This pool is comprised of decentralised stablecoins and generates yield for liquidity providers on Aave, Compound, Euler and Fraxlend integrating liquidity provision and optimised lending under one roof in order to function as a base liquidity layer for decentralised stablecoins and other assets.</p><p><a href="https://medium.com/@BalancerGrants/dynamo-is-using-balancer-boosted-pools-to-build-yield-optimised-liquidity-512fbb5b08a0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Original Medium resource</a></p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Rohmanus</name>
            <uri>https://twitter.com/RohmanusC</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Max Entropy</name>
            <uri>https://twitter.com/0xMaxEntropy</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>greenbergz</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/justingreenberg</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Eike Caldeweyher</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/f3rmion</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="balancer" term="balancer"/>
        <category label="development" term="development"/>
        <category label="grant" term="grant"/>
    </entry>
</feed>